meme.li 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Meme Generator

## General

Your privacy is of extreme importance to us. In order to better understand what kind of information we collect and the way we use such information, please read our privacy policy below.

## User information

Some information about you is being collected by us when you take the following actions among others: site registration, newsletter subscription, form and/or survey filling, placing an order and/or by any other means that is in accordance with and subject to prevailing Israeli Law.

## Details and information collected

Visiting the site can be anonymously. However, some actions, as previously mentioned, may require you to provide us with specific details such as: full name, phone number, mobile phone number, mailing address, e-mail address, ID number and credit card information or social security number.

We may also collect the following information: information about your use of this website, information about transactions carried out over this website and/or any other information that you send and/or upload and/or publish on the website.

## Online Information Only

This privacy policy applies solely to information collected through your online use of our web site.

## Use of the collected information

The information mentioned above will be used to:

  1. Enable and Enhance your access to and use of the web site's services;
  2. Personalize the web site and its services for you;
  3. Improve the customer services;
  4. Better administer this website;
  5. Supply to you the services and/or the products that you purchase;
  6. Send you statements, Marketing communications, periodic emails and invoices regarding the services and/or the products;
  7. Process transactions made by using the web site;
  8. Publish information about you on the web site.

We may disclose your personal information to our agents or sub-contractors or any other third party for these purposes. However, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose personal information if and when we believe that such release is appropriate and/or needed to comply with the law, to abide by a court ruling and/or order, to protect our rights and other parties' rights, and/or property and in order to enforce our website's policies.

Email addresses provided by our web site users for logging on and/or order processing will be used for the sole purpose of sending users information and updates relevant to your use of the website as well as your orders.

If and when you would prefer stop receiving marketing materials and/or future emails, please follow the unsubscribe instructions that are detailed at the bottom of each email we send you.

## Security

We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Our company takes significant measures in order to ensure the safety of the personal information our users are required to provide, for the purposes placing an order or accessing, entering, submitting and/or altering the personal information given by the user.

Our company guarantees your e-commerce transactions to be secure and safe. All of the transactions are transmitted trough a secure socket layer (SSL), which encrypts the personal information before it is sent and accessed by those who have special access rights to such systems and are required to keep this personal data secret and confidential.

Your sensitive information will be stored on our secure and encrypted servers.

User's personal information will never be shared outside our company without the user's consent, except under conditions mentioned above.

## Use of cookies

A cookie, also known as a web cookie, browser cookie, and HTTP cookie, is a piece of text stored by a user's web browser.

Our company uses cookies to monitor and analyze data about website traffic, to remember and analyze items that are part of the user's browsing history and/or shopping cart and save the specific user preferences for future use of our website.

We may contact and enter into agreement with third party service providers to help us use our website's traffic more efficiently.

Those companies are unauthorized to make any use of the personal information collected by our company for other purposes except improving our business.

Cookies can be blocked through your browser settings. This option will cause some services the web site offers to malfunction. A user can still use some services on the website if cookies are blocked, however the services will not run in their optimal state.

## Advertisments

Our website includes commercial content such as advertisements and marketing material that are posted on behalf of various service providers, advertisers or users, who seek to offer goods or services for sale.

We are not responsible for any of the said material, nor for any consequence of user reliance on such material.

We do not recommend and/or encourage you to purchase the goods or the services offered in such material. The responsibility for any of such material lies solely in the hands of the entity who published it.

For advertising, marketing and business development, our company may use any information that is not personally identifiable.

## Third party links or services

Our site may offer and/or include services and/or products that are being supplied by third party companies and/or entities. These entities have their own privacy policies and terms of use.

Our company does not take any responsibility and/or liability regarding the activity and services of these third party companies. For more on how we work with third parties please refer to our Terms and Conditions page.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are committed to protecting children's privacy. This web site is not intended for the use of children under the age of 15. All of our services and products are intended for the use of people who are at least 15 years of age. Therefore, we will do our best to try to avoid collecting any information from anyone under 15 years of age.

However, because this is a website which is intended for the use of adults and because we have no means to monitor the age of the website's users, we encourage parents and other adults to explain to children that this website is not intended for their use.

## Terms and Conditions

The use of this website is governed by its Terms and Conditions ("The Terms") which elaborate on the use, waivers, limitations of liability and disclaimers. IN USING THIS WEB SITE YOU ARE DEEMED TO HAVE READ AND AGREED TO THE TERMS.

You can find the Terms and Conditions of the use of our website at terms of use.

## Your Consent

By using our website, you acknowledge and agree to this privacy policy and The Terms.

## Updating this statement

We may change and/or edit and/or update this privacy policy by posting a new version on privacy policy.

You are encouraged to check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Contact Us

With any further questions and/or requests, regarding privacy issues and this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us using the information below.

http://meme.li info@meme.li
